《异形魔怪3》
（阿根廷恰可平原）
我们之所以会站在这里
Si mI amiga. We are completamente seguros here…
是经过我仔细选择的
because I've selected my position carefully.
战斗的第一原则 了解你的敌人
First rule of engagement: Know your enemy.
第二原则 懂得在何处与他交战
Second rule: Know where to engage him.
你继续让引擎转动
You've kept your engines running.
我要它们释放出
I want maximum heat emissions…from these coordinates.
最大的热力来
Mucho caliente. Comprende?
时间 清晨五点
The time, 5:00.
地点 恰可平原南方七公里处
The place, seven klicks south of EI Chaco.
情况
The situation:
两星期前曾接到报告 附近有一条突袭蟒活动
A single graboid reported in the area two weeks ago.
过去十一年中 突袭蟒共出现过三次
The third appearance of these underground carnivores in the last 11 years.
由于地方当局的疏失
Unfortunately, lack of action on the part of locaI authorities…
使怪兽得以变形
has allowed the creature to
如今它已进入 第二阶段的生命周期中
metamorphose…into the second stage of its life cycle,
已创造出六支尖叫兽
producing six shriekers…
那是一种贪婪的双性动物
a voracious, hermaphroditic life-form…
只要有充足的食物 它每几分钟就能复制一次
which can double in number every few minutes by eating sufficient food.
以今天来讲 它们的食物是鸡
In this case, chickens.
满满一卡车的鸡
A truckload of chickens.
现在红外线监视器 侦测到一群尖叫兽
Infrared monitoring now indicates the shrieker herd…
正越过彭巴斯草原向我们接近
moving across the pampas toward us…
距离我们将近300米
closing at less than 300 meters.
290 280
290. 280.
我利用战斗上的技巧 引导尖叫兽群离开人口聚集处
I've managed to lead the shrieker herd away from civilian population.
所使用的战技包括坐牛酋长
My tacticaI approach is utilize various maneuvers…
在小大角羊河之役的技巧
demonstrated by Sitting Bull at Little Bighorn…
和第二次世界大战中 隆美尔北非之役的战法
and Field MarshaI RommeI during the North Africa campaign.
目的是要建立一个适当的屠宰区
The idea being to set up a proper kill zone.
顺便提一下它们的作战技巧
I should take this opportunity to point out their zero tacticaI skills.
由于没有眼睛和耳朵 它们只能感觉到热能
Lacking eyes or ears, they can sense only heat and…
朋友们 要有耐心
Patience, mI amigo.
根本就不用担心
Nothing to worry about…
因为这次我有最合适的武器
because for once I have the proper tooI at hand.
你们在找热能吗？
Looking for a little heat?
还有什么问题？
Any questions?
（完美镇）
（正牌突袭蟒）
（最冷的啤酒）
（房地产销售处）
（完美谷牧场）
伯特 欢迎你回来
Burt, welcome home.
我们在电视上 看到你开炮的英姿
We saw you on CNN shooting that cannon thing.
双管点五零的高射炮真过瘾
DuaI.50 antiaircraft turret mount.
米格 真高兴见到你 那是什么鬼东西
Good to see you, Miguel. What the hell is that?
是雷诺来的房地产商 他们想分割整个山谷
Some reaI estate guys out of Reno. They want to cut up the valley into parceIs.
- 他们在做梦 - 我也是这么说的
- That'll be a cold day in hell. - That's what I told them.
当你离开时
Burt, while you were gone…
好多的水泥卡车开到你家去
there was this conga line of cement trucks going up to your place.
你到底在建什么东西
What are you building up there?
我在建突袭蟒的地底路障 是我自己设计的
I installed an underground graboid barrier, my own design.
一个包上钢的大水泥箱 有两英尺厚
Big cement box, two-feet thick, steeI reinforced…
建在地下 围绕着整个房子的地基
completely surrounding my compound…
现在终于能安心睡觉了
sides and bottom. Now I can sleep nights.
都已经过了十一年了吧
Come on, Burt. What's it been, 11 years?
那也不能掉以轻心
No reason to lower your guard.
欢迎回来
Burt, welcome home.
你要装电脑条码机吗？
Put in a bar code reader?
他们能用它来建立 我的购买档案
Jodi, they can use that to build a profile on all my purchases.
伯特 欢迎回来
Burt, welcome home.
是的 下一次 他们会问我要DNA样品
Yeah, welcome. Next they'll want a sample of my DNA.
你怎么样？
How have you been?
还可以吧
I guess I'm getting by.
还可以？
Getting by?
你干的比你叔叔要好得多
You're doing better than your uncle ever did.
经营零售业 若不能夺得先机 就活不下去
In retail, if you're not three steps ahead, you're one step behind.
要看信吗？好吧
You want your mail? Yeah, I guess.
「完美谷牧场」
Perfection Valley Ranchettes.
他们已向所有的人出价了
They've been making offers to all of us.
要我替你归档吗？
Shall I file it for you?
好酷的表 是那些阿根廷人送给我的
CooI watch. Gift from the gauchos.
它是利用超音波
It continuously updates its time to the nanosecond…
直接与科罗拉多的铯原子钟连接
by connecting directly to the cesium clock in Colorado…
准确度高达十亿分之一秒
via uItrasonic frequency.
超出人耳的范围 只有狗耳能听到
Well above our normaI range of hearing, but it'll give a dog fits.
你有帮我带一些突袭蟒 或尖叫兽的尸块回来吗？
Right. So, were you able to get me graboid or shrieker parts
像嘴 触须或爪子？
Beaks, tentacles, claws?
你做的似乎有点过份
Aren't you overdoing all this a little?
这些东西会让我们名气大增
Burt, this stuff is our claim to fame.
中国有熊猫 澳洲有无尾熊
China has pandas. Australia has koalas.
而我们有这家伙
And we've got these…
就算是绝种也没关系
even if they are extinct here.
你想把山谷变成主题乐园吗？
Are you trying to turn the valley into a theme park?
你朋友不就搞得有声有色
It worked for your friends, EarI and Grady.
我只是为过活而动脑筋罢了 可是这…
I'm just fighting for my piece of the leisure dollar. But this…
这就是你所谓的 主题乐园的标准人选
this is your theme park kind of guy.
「杰克沙漠突袭蟒探险团 终生难忘的巨兽经验」
"Desert Jack's Graboid Adventure, "
他是何方神圣？
who the hell is this yahoo?
在你离开时他搬到这里来
He moved in while you were gone,
开始带观光客 作突袭蟒探险的生意
started this business…taking people out on graboid safaris.
我真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
你们一定要相信 各位先生女士们 一切都是真的
Believe it, ladies and gentlemen.
这里并不是模拟的主题乐园
This is no theme park simulation here.
你们正置身在 突袭蟒的中心点上
You are in the heart of graboid country.
这些地下猛兽 这些为生存而战的居民们
These savage subterrestriaIs…these death-dealing denizens of dirt…
在十一年前首度在此对抗
first appeared about 11 years ago.
千万别眨眼 随时要准备行动
Yeah, you keep your eyes peeled, your mind and body centered.
这些怪兽随时会跳出来
These things can jump up at any moment.
搞什…
What the…
别怕 只是长耳野兔罢了
Just a jackrabbit, folks. Just a jackrabbit.
深呼吸然后放松 很好
Breathe and release. There you go.
这些家伙…
These suckers,
我曾看到它们窜出五十英尺高 就象火山一样…
I've seen one jump…clear 50 feet out of the ground, like a volcano.
一口就吞下一台大卡车 地面上只留下一个大黑洞
Swallowed a semi-truck whole. Now that's what I call roadkill.
这可是真的… 这里是它们的主要猎食区
I tell you, yes, friends, this whole area is a major feeding ground.
过了那个山脊有个牧羊人
Just over that ridge there is where a simple shepherd…
他的身体和羊群全被怪兽吃掉
named Old Fred lost his herd of sheep.
最后只剩下一个头颅
Yeah, and everything eIse from the neck down.
正如我所说的 我们已经到了 突袭蟒活动的中心
Now as I said, we're in the heart of graboid country.
就是这里
Right in the heart of it.
好象有人来了
Whoa! Looks like we have company, folks.
是突袭蟒吗？
Man. Is that a graboid?
好象是「警报」
Yeah, looks like it.
快回去 否则脚就没了
Get back, son, you're going to lose a limb now.
天啊
Oh, God!
怎么那么多 镇静点
It's flooded! Calm down, lady!
它看到我们了吗？
Has it spotted us yet?
不知道 我还看不出来 只看出它大得离谱
I don't know. I can't tell. But it's bigger than I've ever seen. Look!
天啊
Oh, God!
它过来了 不要惊慌
Here it comes! Take controI of yourself, don't panic.
快点 它过来了
Keep going. Come on. Moving in!
我们得赶快离开这里
Well, we'd better get the hell out of Dodge!
希望这次能够发动
Come on now.
发动了 这就是所谓的神迹
We got it. It's called divine intervention.
有杰克在你们会安然无恙的
Just stick with Jack, you're going to make it back.
那里有一条
That's one.
它好象闻到我们的味道 我以为它是听声音的
I think he picked up our scent.
- 我就是这个意思 - 听声音
- Thought they only hunt by sound. - That's what I meant, sound.
四
Four!
好啦 渴死我了
All right, baby. Been waiting for you.
来一瓶吧
Come to Daddy.
你们先跳到这个岩石上
Come on now, hop on this here rock.
来 把手给我
Here you go. Here you go. Give me your hand, darling. Come on.
很好 别让帽子飞了
All right. Hang on to your hat now. Here's the rest of us.
大家都在吗？我来数数看
We got everybody now?
一 二 三 四 五 很好 全在这里
Let's see here, one, two, three, four, five.
看来我们要等上一阵子
That's good. Well, I think we just best wait it out a spell.
你看要等多久？
How long do you think it will be?
夫人 时间就象条无止境的河流
Well, ma'am, time is the eternaI river.
我们不能逆流而上
I suggest we not swim upstream.
这里可真热
Damn, it's hot out here.
有人想来瓶冰凉的啤酒吗？
Anybody up for an ice-cold beer?
本地啤酒三块一瓶 进口啤酒四块半一瓶
I got $3 a bottle domestic, $4.50 imported.
这里还有新鲜果汁
Also, might I recommend my fresh fruit juices?
有芒果巨兽 葡萄突袭蟒
Monster Mango. Graboid Grape.
再加一块钱 就可以保留瓶子当做纪念品
For a buck extra, you can keep the souvenir glass.
晚上这里还会发光 你们看
Glows in the dark. Look at that.
请输入密码
Please enter access code…
否则一级安全程式 将在十秒内起动
or LeveI 1 security program will be activated in ten seconds.
九 八 七
Nine seconds, eight seconds, seven seconds…
六 五…
six seconds, five seconds.
谢谢你们的参加 我们今天真幸运
Thank you for your business. I'd say we got pretty lucky out there today.
- 一点也不错 - 我们看到的只是尘土而已
- Absolutely. - All we saw was dust.
相信我 光看到尘土是运气
That's all you want to see, believe me, son.
你们顺着柏油路一直开 就能出山谷
Stay on the blacktop now till you're clear out of the valley.
别忘了介绍你的朋友来参加
tell your friends about us.
我得补点冷饮
Got to restock the cooler here.
今早那袋冰你还没付钱
By the way, you didn't pay me for that bag of ice this morning.
我以为那是送的
Well, you know, I thought it was complimentary ice.
我这里可是在做生意呀
I'm in business here, Jack.
我也是呀 所以你应该以批发价卖给我
So am I. I've been thinking you ought to sell me my refreshments at wholesale.
- 原因呢？- 那是自然界的共存法则
- Because? - It's a part of our symbiotic relationship.
共存法则 真有你的
Symbiotic relationship. That's a good one, Jack.
其实所有的东西都有关联
You see, Jodi, all things are related.
我的生意会带给你生意
My business brings business to your business.
依我估计至少让你的生意 增加五十个百分点
Probably like an increase of about, approximately around…50%.
实际上
Actually…
是二十二个百分点 还要加上持续的不确定性
22%, with questionable sustainability.
「持续的不确定性」
Questionable sustainability?
你有企划案吗？
Do you have a business plan?
何必计划得那么多 我深信宇宙的涨潮和退潮原理
I try not to plan too much. I trust in the ebb and flow of the universe.
依如今经济发展的趋势看 必须要有计划才能成长
You have to plan to be a viable entity in today's economic landscape.
例如我在建立产品特性上 已进入第三阶段
See, me, I'm in phase three of establlshing my product identity.
就象是比恩邮购公司的 独木舟啦 户外活动用品啦
You know, L.L. Bean, "canoey, " outdoorsy.
蓝安服饰公司的 高尔夫俱乐部啦 帆船啦
Land's End, "goIf clubby, " "sailboaty."
我晓得了 象张氏杂货店的
I see. I see. Chang's Market.
沙漠啦 地下怪兽啦
Is that, you know, that, kind of "deserty", "underground monstery"?
没错
Exactly.
好吧
All righty.
希望你能顺利的成长
Sure hope nothing stops you from becoming a viable entity…
否则我会很伤心
because I hate when that happens.
我会把冰记在你的帐上
I'm billing you for that complimentary ice.
这种粘土实在很棒
You know, I really like this clay.
在窑里烧也不会裂 可惜太贵了
It doesn't crack in the kiIn, but it is so expensive.
如果你订两百磅 就给你打个九折
I can get 10% off if you order 200 pounds.
那还是太贵了
Yeah, I can't even afford that.
- 嗨 乔蒂 - 敏蒂
- Hi, Jodi. - Hey, Mindy.
你能把这交给杰克吗？
Can you give these to Jack when he comes in?
- 没问题 - 放在桌上就行 谢谢你
- Sure. Throw them on the table. - Thanks.
敏蒂 你应该替他补起来
Mindy, I think Jack was expecting you to sew those pants…
而不是用胶布贴起来
not just stick tape on them.
妈 贴起来已经足够了
Mom, tape is a totaI statement.
象我们这类人就能完全了解
People like Jack and I understand that.
我以前偏爱用安全别针
I was into safety pins, myself.
- 嗨 伯特 - 嗨
- Hey, Burt. - Hey, Mindy.
敏蒂 我以为你上学去了 我妈没告诉你吗？
I thought you were off at school.
我们付不起学费只好退学
Mom didn't tell you? I had to drop out. We couldn't afford the tuition.
所以才回来 到琵市的奥比速食餐厅打工
So, I'm back working at the Arby's down in Bixby…
继续在我妈的压力下过活
and trying to survive my mother.
希望将来会有所改变
Well, I hope things work out.
谢谢
Thanks.
里面有冰啤酒
Beer is inside.
下来时要小心点
There you go. Watch your step.
伯特
Gummer?
是你吗？
Is that you?
真是你
It is, isn't it?
天呀 能见到你是我的荣幸 我叫杰克
Damn! ReaI pleasure to meet you, sir. Jack Sawyer.
由于对你们的崇拜
I've started up this little tour business.
我特别在这里经营旅游生意
Kind of an homage to you guys.
如果你肯参与的话 铁定会使我增光不少
I would be honored if you would consider being a part of it.
你只要签签名 来点武器示范就行了
Sign a few autographs…maybe a little weapons demonstration.
妈 替我和怪兽拍一张
Mom, take a picture of me with the tremor.
好主意
Cute idea.
它们叫做「突袭蟒」
They're called graboids.
喂 你们快来这边 看看这位是谁 快过来呀
Come on over here, folks. Look who I've got for you. Come on down!
这就是传奇人物伯特
The legendary Mr. Burt Gummer himself.
- 妈 就是那个使枪的人 - 哇 真是他
- Mom, it's the gun guy. - It is.
你就站在这里 挺起胸膛
Here, MiIton.
你不介意吧？挺胸呀
Stand right here, up straight. You don't mind, do you?
显出高高在上的英姿 再高点
Straight, honey. Nice and tall. Taller!
说「突袭蟒」
Say "graboids."
- 「突袭蟒」 - 太棒了 谢谢你伯特先生
- Graboids. - Oh, great. Thank you so much, Mr. Goober.
你怎么又有那种怪怪的表情 怎么搞的？
You had that look on your face. What was that about?
妈 你又来了
Don't start, Mom.
你看他们已经深信不疑了
They're out of their gourd right now.
我的心灵之声告诉我
My inner voice has been telling me…
咱们注定会一起合作
you and I are destined to work together.
愿意吗？
What do you think?
如果我有心灵之声的话 一定会让我告诉你快滚蛋
If I had an inner voice it'd be telling me to tell you to get lost.
反正不急在一时
Well, you know, take your time.
你就慢慢考虑 以后再告诉我
You just think about it and get back to me now.
他会想通的
He'll come around.
喂 巴佛 你少色了
Buford! Get your head out of your pants.
我只是在看风景而已
I was just looking at the scenery.
你口水都流出来了 去替下个团准备特效
Drooling on yourself. Go set up for the next group.
你也不必这么凶嘛
You don't have to be so mean.
老兄 我真想教训你一番
Boy, you're about as sharp as a bowling ball.
算你狠
Yeah, tough guy.
嗨 敏蒂
Hi, Mindy.
头颅被撕裂
That skull was ripped wide open, boy.
- 眼珠掉出来 - 太恐怖了
- Eyeballs popping out. - Ugly!
好了 正如我所说的 你们已置身在 突袭蟒的中心点
Now as I said, you're in the heart of graboid country.
你们正在中心点上
Yeah, you're right in the heart of it.
我郑重的警告各位
Let me tell you something, boys…
你们正在他妈的中心点上
you're right in the frigging heart of it!
- 你看到了吗？- 我的天 你们看 越来越近了 那是什么？
- Honey, did you see that? - Sweet Jesus! Look!
车子怎么发动不起来
Having a little engine trouble, folks.
大家不要惊慌
Stay calm. Stay calm.
- 到哪里去了？- 有杰克在你们会安然无恙的
- Where is it? - Stick with Jack, you'll make it back.
小心 别让帽子飞啦 救命呀 突袭蟒来啦
Hold on to your hats. Help, help, graboid attack.
你们整天就干这些事吗？
This is what you guys do all day?
我没有恶意 但看起来实在很无聊
I mean, no offense, Buford, but it's like tragically lame.
和以前比起来 这份差事要好得多
This is a good living. Compared to what I was doing before.
你以前干什么？
Which was?
我负责清理公路上的动物死尸
Well, I was…shoveling roadkill for the county.
那我了解
Okay, I get you, but…
可是为什么杰克愿意浪费时间
why is Jack wasting his time…
和那些乡下人穷搅和呢
scamming yahoos with this Scooby-Doo routine?
他应该能找到 一堆比这个要好的工作
I bet there are a zillion better things a guy like that could do.
我想他一定是被女朋友甩了 或发生过什么不幸的事
I bet he's nursing a broken heart. Or something totally tragic.
他一定想找个 了解他的人倾诉一番
I bet he's just dying to talk to somebody who understands him.
好 全都到齐了吗？
All right, we got everybody now?
这里真热 谁要来瓶冰凉的啤酒？
Damn, it's hot out here. Anybody up for an ice-cold beer?
你知道在这大太阳下
You know, I couldn't help but notice that you're getting…
你的皮肤被晒得很红
awfully red out here in the sun.
你一定要玩刀吗？
Do you really have to keep doing that?
你们这批探险团 到什么时候才结束？
When is this tour going to be over, anyway?
你似乎不喜欢我陪你
You don't enjoy my company, huh?
一般男人会因此而生气的
A man could take offense at that.
那是什么？
What's that?
不要动
Freeze!
他没事吧
Is he all right?
别嚼了 快把嘴里的东西吐掉
快啊
快找个东西丢出去
把你的手给我
Come on, give me your hand!
这东西根本不是真的 大家别说话 她是谁？
This thing is not even real! Everybody, shut up!
- 听她的 - 另一个人又是谁
- listen to her! - Who's that
拜托闭嘴
Shut the hell up!
杰克的吉普车比它快 但我们先要让它转移目标
Jack's jeep can outrun it, but we need a diversion.
制造噪音最有效 大家去找些东西来
Some noise! Everybody, grab something.
这给你 象什么呢？
Like what?
随便什么都行
Like anything.
我们把东西朝那边扔
We're going to throw stuff out that way…
然后跳进车里朝这边开
then we're going to pile in the Jeep and hauI ass.
懂了吗？好
Got it? Okay. On three.
数到三就扔 一 二 三
One, two, three! Okay!
我的照相机呢？你把我全新的照相机给扔了
Where's my camera? You threw away my brand-new camera?
这次我们早就准备好了
This time we're ready for you.
你运来的突袭蟒 有四个触须而不是三个
This shipment of graboids has four tentacles instead of three.
看起来怪怪的 没人会买的
They look ridiculous. Nobody is going to buy them.
- 那是什么？- 是伯特的警报器
- What the hell is that? - It's Burt's siren.
突袭蟒警报？不可能
The graboid ladder? It can't be real, Nancy.
一定是真的 否则不会响 快走吧
He wouldn't blow the siren unless it was for real.
希望敏蒂没事 千万别做傻事
I hope Mindy's okay. Hope she doesn't do something stupid.
我决不付钱
I'm not paying for them!
我认为整个过程太小孩玩意了
If you ask me, there's something very amateurish about this operation.
你让游客 处于生死攸关的环境中
You take people into a life-or-death situation,
居然连枪都是假的
and you don't have a reaI gun?
你有营业执照吗？
Are you even licensed to do this?
你要看突袭蟒不是看到了吗
You wanted to see a graboid, you saw a graboid.
我建议你们立刻朝西雅图出发 沿路千万别停车
I advise you to hit the highway and don't stop till you reach Seattle.
你要赔我那个照相机
I expect you to pay for that camera!
敏蒂 到底是怎么回事？
Mindy, thank God! What's going on?
妈 它们回来了 我们才在那里遇到它 是活生生的突袭蟒吗？
Mom, they're back. We just made it out. Graboids? Live ones?
伯特 我们找到一条 巴佛被它杀了
Burt, we found one. Son of a bitch killed Buford.
才一下子的功夫… 巴佛就被它吞进肚子里去了
I mean, boom and he was gone.
它像鲸鱼那么大
The thing is like the size of a whale.
对 我见过它们
Yep, I've seen them.
伯特 我们可以下来了吗？
Burt, is it okay? Can we come down?
下来吧 它们离得还远
Come on down. They're not close.
你查过我给你的地震仪吗？
You check the seismo-monitor I gave you?
不怎么好用 电池好象没了
It's not working very well. I think the batteries are dead or something.
别这样嘛 都已经十一年啦
Come on, Burt. It's been, what, 11 years?
这是伯特 请说话
Burt here. Talk to me.
刚刚的警报是真的吗？
Burt, was that siren noise for real?
是真的
Affirmative. No me chingas.
- 你在屋顶上吗？- 我当然在屋顶上
- You on your roof? - Damn right, I am.
你查过地震仪吗？附近有突袭蟒活动吗？
Check your seismo-monitor? Any graboid activity near your ranch?
那根针已经弯了 我一直想修它
Burt, that aeriaI thing, it got bent, man. I've been meaning to fix it.
那大家最好待在一起
Well, now it's all hands on deck, Miguel.
我建议你马上开车 以稳定的速度离开
So, I suggest you bug out asap, maintain a steady speed on your truck…
到总部张氏杂货店集合 你听到了吗？
and report to HQ at Chang's, you copy that?
- 好在只有三条 - 你怎么知道？
- Good news, there are only three. - How do you know that?
几年前 我装置了地下监视器 监听整个山谷
A few years ago, I put a geophone monitoring system around the valley.
资料传送到我的手提电脑 以便做三角测量
Data transmits to my laptop, gets triangulated.
是根据瑞妲的地质研究而得的
It's all based on Rhonda LeBeck's geologicaI research.
- 我店里有卖她所有的书 - 漫画最好看
- I sell all her books. - The comics were better.
没错
Totally.
它们从北方逐渐接近 就象上次一样
They're moving slowly down from the north, just like last time…
从杰兹米平地直达
from Jasmer quadrangle, straight down the valley…
- 卡里波平地 - 他在讲什么？
- into Calypso quadrangle. - Huh?
- 就是指仙人掌平地 - 何必说得那么复杂
- I think he means Cactus Flats. - Why can't he just say it?
那我们该怎么办
So, what do we do?
你可以结束你的丛林探险团
Your little jungle boat ride is over, mister.
- 该是钓大鱼的时候了 - 那我们该怎么做呢？
- Time to fish or cut bait. - So what do we do?
但是 伯特 这次我们不能再单独行动
Burt, excuse me, but we're not cut off this time.
去扮演国民兵的角色了
We don't have to act like militia nitwits.
我们可以去求救
We'll call for help.
由于你们没有维护机器 更没有好好监视它们
Nancy, since no one has bothered to maintain their seismic equipment…
所以它们什么时候开始活动
we don't know how long they've been active…
什么时候会变成尖叫兽 我们一点概念也没有
and therefore have no idea when they may become shriekers.
绝对等不及让当局来插手 一切要靠自己
We can't wait for the authorities. We are the authorities.
那我们该怎么做？
What do we do?
去追捕它们
We hunt them down.
杀光它们
We wipe them out.
黎明就出发
We can go at dawn.
这东西真不错
These are perfect.
你有多少存货 十一个
How many do you have in stock? Eleven.
我全部征收
Need to requisition all of them.
那我拿得到钱吗？
Requisition. Am I getting reimbursed?
- 今天不行 - 这东西真行吗？
- Not today. - How does it work?
不过是部玩具车罢了 我还是搞不懂
Killing them with a toy truck?
- 突袭蟒靠感觉掠食 - 就是声音 这个我知道
- Graboids hunt by sensing… - Sound. I know.
当它听到玩具车的声音 就会像猫一样去追它
A graboid hears a toy truck, goes after it just like a cat to catnip.
- 漫画里曾提到过 - 等它把它吞下去 你就引爆炸药
- It's in the comic books. - When he swallows detonate the explosive.
轰 它就呜呼哀哉了
Boom! End of worm.
可是我们没有炸药呀
Explosive. Where are we going to get the explosive?
官方虽没有正式批准
This, not being an officially sanctioned event…
但我仍旧提供本人的设计…
I've provided something of my own design.
伯特没问题 他知道该怎么做
Don't worry about Burt. He knows what he's doing.
把这些记在我的账上
It's like his thing. Put these on my tab.
快把货装好马上出发 你根本没账嘛
Mount up and move out. You don't have a tab!
杰克 我和你一起
Jack, I'm going with you.
不行 你不能和他一起
No, you're not.
有什么事吗？
Yes, sir?
早安 是伯特先生吗？
Good morning. Mr. Gummer?
早安
Morning.
- 我是法兰克探员 - 我表弟已经…
- Agent Frank Statler. - My cousin, he went back to Mexico.
我已经申请过营业执照
I've filed for my business license.
人民的武装权是不容侵犯的
The right to bear arms shall not be infringed.
我们是内政部的
Department of the Interior.
这位是土地管理局的 外勤探员洛斯克
This gentleman is Field Agent Rusk of the BLM…
和美国国家博物馆的 古生物学家安德鲁博士
and Dr. Andrew Merllss, Director of Paleontology at Smithsonian.
我们还有事要办 没时间闲聊
We don't have time to chat. We've got work to do.
你们不能去追捕突袭蟒
Not if it's hunting graboids, you don't.
是我叫他们来的
I called them, Burt.
我被下令严守 濒临绝种动物法中 第1472-B条款
I was granted authority to insure adherence to Section 1472-B…
特别保护
of the Endangered Species Act…
沙漠中的大型爬虫
which guards the welfare of large-class desert reptilians.
我下令在完美镇中 不准任何人猎杀突袭蟒
I'm enforcing an immediate ban on hunting of graboids in Perfection Valley.
我养的牛就在那边
Those are my cattle out there, pendejo.
土地管理局的人允许我射杀 任何危害牛群的东西
The BLM man gave permission to kill anything dangerous to my cattle.
不论是野狼 郊狼 或是突袭蟒
EI lobo, eI coyote and eI graboid.
所有土地管理局的人都归他管 如今他也得听我的指挥
Your BLM man reports to him, who reports to me…
我告诉你们不准杀戮突袭蟒 就这么简单
and I'm here to tell you there will be no more killing of graboids.
若让它们活下去 我们就会成了濒临绝种的动物
So, we let them live, and we become the endangered species.
你曾经两次在两大洲 帮助当地政府
You have been instrumentaI in the eradication of the oldest…
消灭这种地球上
rarest species on earth. Not once, .
最古老 罕见的生物
but on three separate occasions, on two continents.
我是替那两国政府 保卫他们的人民和财产
Defending lives and property, a guest of two foreign governments.
- 你可知道民众在抗议吗？- 什么民众 是这里的吗？
- Are you even aware of the public outcry? - Public? Not this public.
我们的指令很简单
Our mandate is simple:
调查 活捉并运回去做研究
To investigate, trap and transport at least one creature for study.
「活捉并运回去」
Trap and transport?
等你们发现做不到的时候 它们已变形成尖叫兽了
When you find out that's impossible, we'll be overcome with shriekers.
当我们发现对民众有威胁时
If we discover there is a threat to public safety…
就会立刻疏散完美镇 无限期的封闭此地
we're prepared to evacuate Perfection Valley and seal it off.
等一下 你要我们离开这里
Wait a minute! You'd make us leave?
我是叫你们来帮忙 不是让你们来赶我们走
That's not why I called you. I called you here to help us.
州长会给你们合理的补偿金 这点你们不用担心
The government will offer compensation for your property. That's a given.
这就是所谓的国家征用权
Eminent domain.
人们居然说我是偏执狂
And people call me paranoid.
我可不同意
I don't think you're paranoid.
我本来是这么想 现在不会了
I do, but not no more.
你这个杂种
Son of a bitch!
「叫我以实玛利」
"Call me Ishmael."
只要你这快绝种的身体
Now if you would kindly lean your endangered carcass…
一超过我土地的界限
over my property line.
我就能以自卫原因杀死你
I'll call your untimely demise self-defense.
又笨又浑的突袭蟒
Damn stupid graboids.
我的店绝不能被征收
Can't afford to get eminent domain out.
我所有的钱全投资在生意上
Every cent I have is tied to this business.
你至少还有个生意
Well, at least you got a business.
你的肢体语言已经表达了一切
Body language says it all.
我们需要来点冰啤酒
Does it say I could use a cold beer?
- 要哪个牌子？- 米勒淡啤酒
- What will it be? - Miller Lite.
在这里手机打不出去 你们可以用公共电话
Yeah, we still don't have cell towers. You can use the pay phone.
就在外面 有民用波段和对讲机
Outside it's CBs and walkie-talkies only.
很好笑
Charming.
你们说要赶我们走 不是当真吧
You guys weren't serious about making us move out, were you?
除非能活捉它们 否则别无他法
Unless we can catch one of them, we may have no choice.
看来这是个小行动
It kind of seems like a small operation.
只不过去抓条突袭蟒罢了
I mean, to catch one whole graboid.
我们的经费不多 对华盛顿来说这不是最高优先
We don't have much of a budget. It's not a high priority in Washington.
但是若真捉到了
But if you did catch one…
你们岂不是光荣返乡吗？
I mean, you boys would go home heroes, right?
在履历表上还可加上一笔
Look good on a resume.
你有什么建议？
And your point would be?
其实唯一熟悉那东西的人
The one guy who knows about these things…
唯一能真正帮你们的人
the one guy who could help out…
已被你三阵出局 正在坐冷板凳呢
is warming up the bench because you took him out of the game.
我并没要他出局
I didn't take him out of the game.
杰克 别忘了他们不是你的朋友
May I remind you, Jack, they are not your friends?
他们是政府官员 完毕
They are government agents. Over.
我只是和他们谈判了一下
Cut me some slack. All I did was negotiate.
- 你做了什么？- 我和他们达成协议
- You did what? - I cut us a deal.
我们替他们抓条突袭蟒 他们就让你继续狩猎
We help catch one live graboid, they give you back your hunting license.
- 了解 还有一个问题 - 说吧
- Copy that. Roger. One question. - Shoot.
你的脑袋短路了吗？
Is your head up your ass for the warmth?
我们以为你会喜欢这个主意
We thought you'd be happy.
- 你不是不想被征收吗？- 抓活的？
- You want to get eminent domained out? - Catch a live graboid?
那些活生生的突袭蟒 用炸药已经很难杀它们
It's hard enough to kill one without saturation bombing.
我告诉他们 没什么事能难倒伯特
I told them, Burt Gummer, he'd come up with something.
这些家伙很聪明 越逼它们就越厉害
The bastards are smart, and they'll get smarter.
但你仍胜过它们呀 我认为你应该接受挑战
You're still here, aren't you? I'd say you're up to it.
伯特先生 你说呢？
So, Mr. Gummer, what do you think?
这是个好机会
Fish or cut bait.
你…
You…
你有麻醉它们的东西吗？
say you have some sort of tranquilizer.
我们用麻醉镖
Yeah, we're using tranq darts.
它会追这些怪物 可惜却无法穿过地面
We got them to chase us, but couldn't get these to penetrate dirt.
我已经去订用钛做的弹头 和更有力的发射枪
I'm ordering titanium tips and a more powerfuI launch gun.
当然啦 尽量去浪费纳税人的钱嘛
Of course, you could squander the taxpayers' money…
我这东西只要四十九块九毛五
but I can get a graboid to swallow this…
只要把麻醉药放在车里 让它吞下去
with this, for $49.95.
它就会失去知觉 而你们就能趁机把它挖出来
Then, if it goes to sleep, you can dig it up…
运到51区或别的地方去
take it back to Area 51…
交给你们那个无知的上司
or whatever fits your plausible deniability.
我不是很了解你的话 我们到底达成协议没有？
I don't understand what you just said, but do we have a deal?
因为我们想知道应该怎么去做
Because we want to know what we should do.
去做你们最擅长的事呀
You guys do what you do best.
就是把简单的事情复杂化
Find something simple and complicate it.
至少他表达了自己的想法 压抑情绪实在很危险
It's good he expresses himself. Repressed emotions can be reaI toxic.
他需要心理医生
He needs counseling.
- 上车 - 什么？
- Get in! - Huh?
你既然把我扯进来 就别想置身事外
You got me into this.
好啊
All right!
有门不会用吗？
Use the door!
不可思议
It's unbelievable!
真是太不可思议了 实在难以置信
Frank, Charlie. It's unbelievable. Unbelievable.
我在所谓突袭蟒
I was doing cores…
最早期的活动地点上 挖掘岩芯样品
out where they recorded the earliest graboid movements. Voila!
在第三个地点挖到这个
I hit this on my third dig.
是蛋 证明它们由蛋孵化而来
It's an egg. I've proven they come from eggs.
我用碳十四年代测定法 测定过了 里面的蛋黄是新鲜的
I've already carbon-dated it. The yolk remains are current…
可是蛋壳却有三百岁了
but the shell is over 300 years old.
新的突袭蟒一定由此而来
Graboids must have come from these.
难道它们沉睡了三百年吗？
They lay dormant for 300 years?
似乎如此
Smoething like this.
电话借我用一下 我得打电话给博物馆
It appears so. I need to use your phone. I must call the museum.
我出五十元向你买
I'll give you $50 for that.
你在开玩笑吧 那是属于美国国家博物馆的
It's going straight to the Smithsonian.
那就一百元吧
All right, all right. $100.
有人要结婚了吗？
Somebody getting married?
首先我们制造噪音 好引诱它靠近
First, we make enough noise to lure one in close.
然后用摇控车做饵
Then, we use the remote-controlled truck as bait.
这些讨厌的政府官员 明明叫他们别插手
Damn feds. I told them to butt out.
好象是别人
No, I think that's somebody else.
伯特 好久不见
Well, Burt. Long time no see.
你看来很不错 你还是老样子 马文？
Looking good. Hard core as ever.
- 马文？- 叫我小马就行了
- Melvin? - It's Mel, actually.
你为什么从不回信 害我跑这么远来找你
How come you never answer our letters, and I got to drive all the way out here?
「完美谷牧场」 是你在卖？
Perfection Valley Ranchettes. That's you?
你还说我永远成不了大业
You said I'd never amount to anything.
我们将要举办大特卖
Look, Burt, we're making some really good deals here.
因为你是我的朋友 所以先告诉你
Between you and me, because we're friends…
我们将以 比别人高一倍的价钱向你收购
you'll get twice what we're offering the others.
你是在这里长大的 怎么这样乱搞一通呢？
What the hell are you doing? You grew up here.
所以才给你这么好的条件
Exactly. I wouldn't wish this place on anybody.
你愿意吗？
So, come on, Burt. What do you say?
你最好立即消失
I'd say, I'll give you a ten-second head start.
大家都准备搬家了 整个郡马上就在我掌握之中
People are folding, Burt, and I got this whole county in my pocket.
你没办法坚持下去的
You can't hold out forever.
我生来就这么顽固
I was born to hold out.
伯特 是不是不对劲了？看来不太对
Burt, is this bad? It looks kind of bad here.
你看呢？
Is this bad? It's…
是突袭蟒 不要动 保持安静
Graboid. One of them spotted us. Freeze. Everybody, quiet.
- 突袭蟒？- 别出声
- A graboid? - Quiet!
你在开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
当真？
For real?
撑下去
Burt! Burt, hang on!
伯特 你要撑下去 我去拿绳子
Hey, Burt, hang on. I'll get a rope.
休士顿 我们有麻烦了
Houston, we have a problem.
- 是伯特吗？- 没错
- Burt? - Affirmative.
你没事吗？
Are you okay?
没有太多时间 空气不够 我的位置在哪里？
Not much time. Only got limited air. What's my 20?
等一下
Hold on. Hold on.
你在西方四分之一英里处
Well, you're about a quarter mile west…
搞错了 你在东方
No, better make that east of me.
离我家只有几英里 就在那儿和它交战
Couple of miles from my place, engage the graboid.
什么？
What?
快开车把它引到我家的前门去
Drive like hell, and lead the bastard through my front gate. Copy?
听到了吗？听到了 但是…
Yeah, I copy, but…
空气没有了 通话完毕
Out of air. Burt out.
等我到达后该怎么办
Burt! Burt, what do I do when I get there?
我该怎么办？
What do I do? Burt! Burt!
来呀 突袭蟒 不怕就来呀
Come on, graboid. Come on, baby, come on!
来呀
Come on, baby.
这家伙上钩啦
We are running with the graboid.
我的妈
Holy shit!
撞个正着
Head-on colllsion.
伯特 你在下面吗？
Burt! Burt, are you down there?
等一下 我马上回来
Hang on. I'll be right there.
你要撑下去 千万别放弃
Hold on, buddy! Hang on, buddy!
继续呼吸
Just breathe!
马上就好
Come on, baby!
你等着
Hang on, buddy!
快好了
Hang on!
就快好了
Come on, baby!
杰克 马文那家伙说你们被攻击了
Jack! That Melvin guy said you got attacked!
你在干什么呀？
What the hell are you doing?
我希望…
I'd prefer…
你们别把这件事…
we keep this…
说出去
to ourselves.
一没人管你们马上就出事
You guys definitely need to be supervised.
这是伯特 你能听到吗？请回答
Burt here. You read me? Come back.
请回答 这是伯特
Come back. Burt here. Come back!
那是突袭蟒吗？
Is that a graboid?
没错 但我们应该看到两条才对
Yeah, but we should be seeing two of them.
政府官员们有消息吗？
Have either of you heard from the feds?
我没法联系到他们 从今早起就音讯全无
I can't raise them. Not since this morning.
大概超出无线电的范围 他们本来在追突袭蟒的
I guess they've gone out of radio range. They were chasing a graboid.
是他们追它而不是它追他们 看来似乎不妙
They were chasing it? It wasn't chasing them? I don't like that.
也许他们把它吓走了
So, maybe they scared it.
天呀 那是什么？
Jesus, what is that?
安德鲁博士 发生什么事？
Dr. Merllss, what happened?
我们在地上
We found the graboid.
找到一条突袭蟒
On the surface.
- 可是它是… - 中空的 分成两半
- It was… - Hollow. Split open.
对 分成两半
Yeah, split open. Split open.
空的 当我们检查它的时候
When we examined it…
我们听到…
the sound.
一种声音 是尖叫的声音
I heard this screaming.
然后它们把我们围起来
And then they were all around us.
动作非常快
So fast!
洛斯克和法兰克
Rusk and Statler…
被撕成碎片
torn to pieces!
它们居然把我的小货车拆开
I hid in my van, but they were ripping it apart.
那时我突然想起… 它们会感应到热能 所以…
I remembered something. Don't let them see body heat.
我把全身喷满灭火剂
I sprayed myself.
好冷 快冻死我了
It's cold. It's so cold.
- 很好 你处理的很好 - 不
- That was good. That was good thinking. - No.
并不完全有效 我恐怕…
Not entirely effective, I'm afraid.
- 南茜 敏蒂 请回话 - 我们在张氏杂货店的屋顶上
- Nancy, Mindy. Come back. - Yes, Burt. We're on Chang's roof.
- 突袭蟒还在到处乱跑吗？- 现在问题更大了
- Is the graboid still around? - We've got a bigger problem now.
- 是尖锐兽吗？- 不对 是尖声兽
- Squealers? - No, screechers.
是尖叫兽 政府官员全被它们杀光了
Shriekers. The government team is all dead.
我的天 你们听好 这些家伙听不到声音
My God. These SOBs don't hunt by sound.
全靠头上的感热器官
They see heat with sensor organs on their heads.
你们必须要隐藏你们的体温 懂了吗？
You've got to hide your body heat somehow. Copy.
隐藏我们的体温？
Hide our body heat?
知道了
Burt, we copy.
现在无法用 地下监听器去追踪尖叫兽
Can't track shriekers with geophones…
只好非法下载红外线卫星影像
so I'm rigged to download infrared satellite images.
当它第一次变形 一共只有六支尖叫兽
When shriekers first emerge, there are only six of them.
一定要在它们找到食物 开始复制前杀了它们
If we can kill them before they find food and multiply, we have a chance.
你们看 那是普雷斯顿干河 开吉普车的路
Okay, here we go. Preston Dry Lake. Jeep trail.
这是我们 那是我们的车 对不对？好 找到了
There we are. Those are our cars, right? Reading the engine heat.
我们可以看到它们了 二 四… 一共有七支
Bingo. We have a visual. Two, four. There are seven of them.
这表示它们已开始复制了
You mean, they're already making more of themselves?
因为它们吃了法兰克和洛斯克 我们得快点行动
Yeah, they munched on Statler and Rusk. We better get moving.
我的命怎么这么苦
I totally hate my life.
要命 还是没看到它们
Damn, I still don't see them.
要怎么对焦距 用我的吧
How do you focus these things? Here, try these.
嗨 最好再查一下卫星
Better get that satellite thing again.
正在查 就在那里 天…
We got you covered. That's it, right there.
变成八支了 它们都吃些什么？
There's eight of them. What are they eating?
郊狼 蜥蜴 蛇 什么都吃
Coyotes, lizards, snakes. They don't care.
这的确很严重
This is really serious.
所以我一直在警告你们
I keep trying to tell you people! How far are your cattle?
你的牛群离这有多远？若让它们找到 我们就完了
If they get to your herd, we're in trouble.
快看那里
Burt, look.
它们要到那个峡谷里去
Look there. They're going into that box canyon over there.
快点 那里只有一条路可以出来
There's only one way out of there.
- 我们可以赶在它们之前到达 - 我跟你一起
- If we get there before… - I'm with you.
没错 然后把它们全杀光
We just roll in and mop those little devils up.
是突袭蟒 快往岩石方向跑
Graboids!
快啊 快点
Go! Go! Come on! Come on!
小心 哇 我的…哪里来的…
Miguel! Where the hell…
我的天
Holy shit.
我从没见过活的突袭蟒
I've never seen a live one.
吓死我了
Holy shit!
我们该怎么办？
What do we do now?
通知南茜和敏蒂去求救
Radio Nancy and Mindy to call for some kind of help.
它居然想吃我的吉普车
Damn thing tried to eat my Jeep.
它的脑袋在想什么
What the hell is it thinking?
你的引擎还在转动 而它只追逐声音
The engine. He went for the noise.
你没看过突袭蟒的漫画吗？上面写得很清楚
Haven't you read the graboid comics? It's all in there.
讨厌的爬虫 汽车的钱还没付清
Freaking slug. I owe money on that thing.
- 杰克 你有对讲机吗？- 在吉普车里 你的呢？
- Jack, you got your walkie? - It's in my Jeep. Where's yours?
在车盖上
On my hood.
看来… 只好等了
Well, I guess we just wait.
真倒霉
Darn! Man!
难道你不担心尖叫兽会逃出来
Are you worried that the shriekers might get out…
跑去吃掉米格的牛群 和整个内华达州吗？
and go eat Miguel's cattle, and, I don't know, the rest of Nevada?
当然担心 但由于我无法控制 只好随他去了
Absolutely. But I do not dwell on that over which I have no control.
所以变成由我来发愁
That's great. I have to do all the dwelling.
那是你的选择
If you choose to.
你猜我发现了什么
You know what I've found?
许多人喜欢积雨云的多变
Most people prefer your dramatic cumulus and nimbus clouds.
我却特别欣赏卷云 它真美
But I've always had a weakness for a cirrus.
那么微弱的挂在天上
Yeah. Wispy, and way up there, you know?
这我倒不知道
I wouldn't know.
- 难道你不向上看吗？- 我很忙
- Well, don't you ever look up? - I'm busy.
忙得没时间看天空？
Too busy to look up?
的确如此 我为生活而打拼
Yeah, as a matter of fact, I am. I'm working for myself here.
当初真该留在旧金山
All right? I could have stayed in San Francisco…
去读个企业管理硕士 年薪赚个十几万
parlayed my MBA into a six-figure income. But, hey.
结果却跑来这里
I'm busting my ass eking a living out here…
- 为了梦想而卖命 - 我知道谋生不容易
- to build something for myself. - I know it's not easy.
但偶尔享受一下也不为过
But I just think you can enjoy yourself while you eke.
谁说我没有享受
Who says I'm not enjoying myself?
其实我不需要向你解释
You know, I don't have to justify myself to you.
（食物大卖场）
「食物大卖场」？你这个小人 居然说只向我买货
Foodmall? You said you bought all your supplies from me!
我并没有签什么约
I don't recall signing any purchasing agreement.
那是口头承诺
It was a verbai commitment. It was understood, okay?
为了你常占据我的电话线 和电脑所做的交换条件
In exchange for tying up my telephone lines and my computer.
你等于省了一笔支出
You're getting free overhead, pal.
还有你错了 我过得很快乐
And, for your information, I do enjoy myself.
是真的
I do.
好在尖叫兽仍在峡谷里
Well, one bit of good news. The shriekers are still in the canyon.
上次在我家外面的就是这条
Got to be the same one I saw outside my house.
它好象得了白化病
Albino, I think.
以前我有支母羊也得了这种病
We used to have a female goat like that.
因此无法生小羊
No kids.
患了不育症
lmpossible. Sterile?
所以它才没变成尖叫兽
Maybe that's why EI Blanco hasn't turned into Los Shriekers.
这个杂…
Son of a…
清晨五点正
5:00, on the dot.
太阳马上就出来了
Be sunrise soon.
还有三十七分三十二秒
In 37 minutes, 32 seconds.
伯特 小心 什么事？
Hey, Burt. Heads up! What? Why, you…
它老跟着你 似乎喜欢上你了
He follows you, Burt. I think he's got a thing for you.
若有那支五十口径的枪 就让它好看
If I could reach my Grizzly.50-caliber, I'd have a thing for him.
那是它们吗？
Is that them?
一定是
It must be!
可是我从没听过它们这么吵闹
But I've never heard them make a noise like that before.
一定又大开杀戒了
Like coyotes…
它们仍在谷里
…with their kill.
不能再等了 我得把对讲机弄过来
They're still in the canyon. Can't afford to wait. I've got to get to my radio.
等一下 用这个试试
Wait, Burt! Try this.
我在马盖先影集里看过
I saw it on a repeat of MacGyver.
那是牙线 我永远随身携带
Dentai floss! I always carry it.
快了
There. There, there.
加油
Yeah. Come on. Come on!
成功了 勾到了
There, you got it. Yes!
南茜 敏蒂 这是伯特 请回话
Nancy! Mindy! Burt here. Come back!
伯特 怎么样了？
What's up?
我们被一条白色突袭蟒盯住了 需要你们的帮助
We're pinned down by…this great white graboid, and we need an assist.
我要你在对讲机里 制造出很大的声音
I want you to make one hell of a racket over the radio. Copy?
你需要噪音 我知道了
You want noise, Burt? I copy that.
- 宝贝 怎么回事？- 伯特打电话来点歌
- Honey, what's going on? - Burt just phoned in a request.
它中计了
He's going for it.
我们赶快行动 还要一支
Here we go. One more.
- 它又回来了 - 是的
- It's coming back! - Yep
它去追饵去了 乔蒂 杰克 我们快走
He's taken the bait. Jodi, Jack, let's move it.
- 这给你 这是大型四发连发枪 它不会咬你的 - 我不知道
- This is yours:.308, four shots in the mag. - I don't know…
杰克 拿着你的韦瑟斯比 我们走
It won't bite you. Jack, grab your Weatherby and let's do this.
- 我的韦瑟…什么？- 你的来复枪
- My "Weather" what? - Your rifle.
- 就在你的枪架上 - 那是假的
- In your gun rack? - The gun is not real.
我向搞电影的人买的
Borrowed it off some movie guy.
这给你 你总知道子弹从那里射出吧
Here. You do know which end the bullets come out of?
- 我在电影里看过 - 你看来有点冷 把衣服穿上
- I've seen movies. - Here. You look cold.
我们现在就去征服尖叫兽
Now, let's go bag our limit of shriekers.
走吧
Come on!
它们应该在转弯的地方
Has to be right around that bend.
- 什么… - 它们在做什么？
- What the… - Jeez, what are they doing?
我不知道
I do not know.
- 不过这可以让它们软化点 - 我还记得这个宝贝
- Let's tenderize them a little. - I remember these babies.
掩护
Cover!
哇 我的天 他还真干上了
Holy shit! He doesn't fool around.
伯特是很认真的
Burt is very committed.
走 我们进攻吧
Come on, come on! Let's hit them!
你们看
Check it out!
它们蒸发了 根本看不到它们的踪迹
Vaporized them! I mean, there's nothing left.
不对 至少会看到尸体 不可能完全不见
No, no. We should see remains. They wouldn't just disintegrate!
- 你怎么知道？- 我以前曾经杀过它们
- How do you know? - I've blown them up before!
那看起来象是 某种脱掉的壳或是皮
It looks like they shed some kind of husk or skin,
- 就象蛇一样 - 看来似乎不妙
- like a snake. - I don't like that.
它们可能又钻回地底
Maybe they went back underground.
先去找我的卡车
Let's just go find my truck.
我蛮喜欢那部卡车的
Burt! I really liked that truck.
你一定很伤心 那是全新的车 对不对？
Man. That has to hurt. It was new, wasn't it?
至少它死得轰轰烈烈
At least it died for a good reason.
里面有各式各样的武器
And my Grizzly Big Bore. My sidearms.
和火药
My ammo.
有东西在动 在围墙后面
Something moved, over behind the fence.
是尖叫兽吗？
It's a shrieker?
已经不是了
Not no more, it's not.
在墨西哥和阿根廷
In Mexico and Argentina,
在它们刚变形的十二小时内 就全被我们消灭了
we killed them before they lived 12 hours.
现在是它们第二次变形
This is what happens when you don't?
所以它们象 病毒一样不断突变吗？
They just keep mutating like a virus?
我也不清楚
I have no idea!
你看那家伙同样能感应热能
Hey, look. That son of a gun has the same heat sensor.
它在追踪我们
Tracking us.
设陷阱去捉它太危险了
It's not smart to track Burt.
它现在在干吗？
What's it doing now?
搞什…
What the…
快开枪 快 瞄准就开枪
Point, shoot! Come on! Point, shoot!
不
No!
喔 天呀
Oh, my God.
都是我的错 我应该早开枪的
I shouldn't have taken that shot. Should have shot sooner!
你又不知道 它会象火箭一样起飞
How could you know it was going to take off like a goddamn rocket?
杰克 把你的对讲机给我
Jack, give me your walkie.
这是伯特 请回答
Nancy, Mindy? Burt here. Come back.
伯特 我们都在这里
Yeah, Burt. We're here.
南茜 你听着 它们…
Nancy, llsten. They…
它们杀了米格
They killed Miguel. He's gone.
天呀 那不是真的
Oh, my God, no.
什么 米格死了？不可能
What, Miguel? No!
南茜 这是乔蒂
Nancy? Jodl here.
尖叫兽现在能飞了
The shriekers can fly now.
你们快离开屋顶 那里不安全 听到了吗？
So, get off the roof. You're not safe up there anymore. Copy?
锁起来 锁上了
Lock it! Lock it.
快走
It's coming back!
你在做什么？它们不是只能感觉到热量吗
What are you doing? They can only see heat!
我并不笨 走 到冷藏柜里去
I'm not dumb, you know! Come on, into the meat locker!
宝贝 我从来没觉得你笨过
Honey, I never thought you were dumb.
蛋 突袭蟒的蛋
An egg. Graboid egg.
所以从突袭蟒到尖叫兽 再演化成这种新的怪物
So it's a graboid, to a shrieker, to one of these here new things…
然后又回到突袭蟒 在生物学上完全可以成立
and finally back to a graboid.
我想它们之所以能够飞翔
It would make sense, biologically. I guess they developed the ability to fly…
是为了把蛋带到远方
so they can carry the eggs as far as possible.
不是吧 你们看 它居然会和空气产生化学作用
Well, look at that. Look at that right there. Reacts with the air.
闻起来象腐烂的豆子
Smells like a bad night of beans.
那是高浓度的辛烷胃酸
Some high-octane stomach acid he has there.
极易反应 几乎象纯钠一样
Extremely reactive. Almost like pure sodium.
不管是什么 它们拼命突变 他妈的屁…
Whatever it is, they work it up there in their ass, see…
- 你说什么？- 所以它们才能飞
- Excuse me? - No, no. That's how they blast off.
每次变形总会出现新的能力
Always something new with these things.
算了 你们的枪全空了 这么快？
No, forget it, you're both empty.
- 空了？- 你开了十发 她开了四发 我的也空了
- Empty? - Already? You fired ten, she fired four. I'm empty, too.
这下可好了
That's just great.
我家离这里三英里远 最好能过去
Great. My place is three miles away. We have to try to make it.
有这些家伙在天上监视 怎么走？
With these honkers doing aerial recon?
我们要想办法隐藏我们的体温
We have to conceal our body heat somehow. All right, it…
我有个笨方法
I can make a dumb suggestion.
我的意思是 既然是我们发现的 就应该由我们替它命名
No! All I'm saying is, we discovered them, right?
我想想看
So, we should name them. Let me think.
飞翔尝试 怎么样？
Okay."Blast-Offers."
或是屁股发射 这个比较好 屁股开花 怎么样？
Or "Butt-Launchers." That's better? "Ass-Blasters!" How's that?
有点象成人电影
Sounds like a porno film.
你们听
llsten!
蹲下来
Get down! Get down!
它没看到我们 我们没事
He didn't see us! We're okay.
- 有约会吗？- 讨厌的阿白
- Lunch date? - Damn! EI Blanco.
你说什么？那条白色的突袭蟒
I'm sorry? White graboid.
正朝着我们过来
He's moving towards us.
连休息一下也不行 走这边
Can't we get a break here? Come on, come on. This way.
这个山脊下全是花岗岩
Beneath this ridge is a solid granite intrusion.
看来阿白只好改路走了
We'll follow it, but EI Blanco will have to go around.
花岗岩？几乎整个峡谷的地质 我都记住了
Granite intrusion? I memorized the valley's geology.
是吗 我也想这么做
Oh, yeah. I been meaning to do that.
把武器给我 你们随意
Give me your weapons and make yourselves at home.
我查一下南茜和敏蒂 是不是也安全无恙
I'll see if Nancy and Mindy got through to the Air NationaI Guard.
哇 这么多选择
Lots of choices.
南茜 敏蒂 这是伯特 请回话
Nancy, Mindy. Burt here. Come back.
伯特呼叫南茜和敏蒂 请回话
Burt calling Nancy and Mindy. Copy?
我买的那些货
You know those supplies I bought?
- 以成本价卖给你好吗？- 有罪恶感了吗？
- How about I let you have them at cost? - Feeling guilty?
南茜 敏蒂 请回话 有一点
Nancy, Mindy. Come back. Yeah.
但最主要的是我想筹旅费
But mostly I'm going to need traveling money.
伯特呼叫南茜和敏蒂
Burt calling Nancy and Mindy. Copy?
你们听到了吗？
You copy?
这是伯特 请回话 南茜？敏蒂？
Burt here. Come back. Nancy? Mindy?
- 南茜 敏蒂 回答我 - 这样说你想离开这里？
- Nancy? Mindy? Talk to me. - So, you'll be leaving?
总不能在 客人会被吃掉的地方做生意
Can't run a business where your customers get eaten.
- 你说的没错 - 南茜 敏蒂 这是伯特 请回话
- Guess not. - Nancy, Mindy, Burt here. Come back!
该死 希望他们没事
Damn it! Hope they got out okay.
咱们的老友阿白终于来了
Our old friend EI Blanco is finally coming this way.
不用担心 这周围能完全抵挡突袭蟒
Not to worry, our perimeter is completely graboid-proof.
可是能抵挡屁股开花兽吗？
But is it Ass-Blaster-proof?
走 我来拿武器
Come on, come on. I'll grab my weapon!
走 快点
Go! Go! Come on!
我们到安全室去
This way, into the safe room!
快
Come on!
封闭它
Seal it!
- 这些是什么 食物吗？- 是MRE 比普通食物还棒
- What is all this? Food? - Better. MREs.
「即食便餐」 是营养成份最高的食物
Most dense, most nutritious food known to man.
我们能在这里待多久
Okay, how long can we wait it out in here?
六 七年吧 这得看怎么分配食物
Six, seven years. Depending on how well you maintain your dietary discipline.
它们居然想把门溶化
Son of a bitch is meIting the door down.
你们这些丁烷屁股开花的混蛋
Damn his butane, butt-blasting ass.
别管了 来这边
Forget that! Here!
- 逃生隧道 - 伯特 我喜欢你
- Escape tunnel! - Burt, I like you.
当然啦 快走
You should! Go on, go on!
如果这些家伙 吃了你的食物会怎样？
What happens if this thing eats your food?
那就会变成军队了
Ass-blaster blitzkrieg.
快走 我来善后
Go on! I'll take care of it.
咱们看谁厉害
Trick or treat, you son of a bitch!
- 那是五加仑的无铅汽油 - 天呀 你想得真周全
- Five gallons of unleaded. - Man. You really go the distance!
没错 我是自毁宗师
Yeah, I'm a masterpiece of self-destruction.
依我计算 火苗到达重装火药点应该…
Fire should reach my stock of reloading powder right about…
就是现在 找掩护
now.
来这边 快走
Come on! Over here. Go, go!
- 伯特？- 又怎么了？
- Burt! - Now what?
伯特 你到哪里去了 我们一直联络不到你
Burt, where've you been? We've been trying to raise you.
- 你绝对不会相信 - 你说
- You won't believe it. - No, try me.
我们抓到一支会飞的尖叫兽
You know those flying shriekers? We've got one!
其实它几乎杀了我们 你猜我们怎么抓到它的？用食物
Well, actually, it almost got us, but you know how we got it?
它吃了我一半的存货
Food! It ate half the food in the store!
现在已进入昏睡状态
If they eat enough, they go into a food coma!
不行 它们会繁殖
No. They multiply!
它们不会 只要继续喂它吃 把你的MRE喂它们就行了
No, Burt, they don't! Just feed it! Give it all your MREs.
伯特 你听到了吗？
Burt, do you copy? Burt?
伯特…
伯特暂时不在
Burt's… Burt is not available at the moment,
但谢谢你的新资料
but thanks for the update, Nancy.
是什么样的神和我玩这种把戏
What kind of Supreme Being would condone such irony?
有句名言是：「神枪手只瞄准自己」
Well, there are those who say, the marksman aims at himself.
你现在需要进入空的境界中
Power of non-attachment. You need to tap into that right now.
杰克 拜托少打禅语啦
Enough with the Zen zingers, all right?
伯特 你要坚持下去
Burt? Maintain.
准备了一辈子 结果成了难民
A lifetime of preparation, and I end up a refugee?
我实在不想说 但我认为在经历过这些爆炸后
I hate to ask, but have we gone through all this
我们最后可能还是被阿白吃掉
just to be eaten by EI Blanco?
爆炸的声音会把它吓跑
The explosions were so loud, they have driven him far away.
你实在应该看那些漫画
You really should read the comics.
怎么还有四支？
There are four more of them?
火能吸引那些 能看到热的肉食动物
Nothing like a fire to attract every heat-seeking…meat-eater in the valley.
- 我们得躲起来 - 到哪去 我已无家可归
- We have to hide. - Where? I have no home!
到废物堆积场去 什么？
Junkyard.
就去废物堆积场
Junkyard! Yeah.
问题是怎么去
We just have to get that far.
大自然供应一切
The universe provides.
- 你想坐船去？- 还有蓝色的防水布 快走
- The universe provides a boat? - And a blue tarp. Come on!
在它们看到以前进去 快点 来呀
Get your heinies up here before they see us! Now, move! Come on!
进去 用它遮住我们
Get in! Put it over yourself!
快遮起来 就象我常说的 有杰克在你们会安然无恙的
Come on! Like I said, just stick with Jack, you're going to make it back.
向左 向左 不 是向右 向左 不…向右
Now, go left. No, no! Right!
- 不要那么多嘛 - 你别变来变去
- Not that far! Now go right! - Make up your mind!
向右
Jack, go right!
天啊
What the heck…
（完美谷牧场预定地）
那个小王八蛋
The little turd.
我们成功了 够我们躲的了…
We made it! Look! Plenty of places to hide!
等等 它没看到我们
Wait. It doesn't see us.
慢慢的离开船
Calmly, get out of the boat.
冷静的朝…
And calmly, just head for…
它看到我们了 快跑
It sees us! Shit! Run!
它追来了
It's coming!
我的天
My God.
- 它到哪儿去了？- 在那里 我可以听到它 我听到了
- It's right there, can you hear it? - I hear it.
- 就在那里 - 我已经说过了
- It's right there. - That's what I said.
我们先离开这里
Let's get out of here.
那是替米格报仇
Yeah! That one's for Miguel!
我们可以休息一下吧
About time we got a break.
其他的都来了
Here comes the rest of them.
要命 它们看到我们了吗？知道我们在这里吗？
God! Do you think they see us? Do they know we're here?
没看到…
No.
看到了
Yeah.
- 快藏起来 - 可以藏在这里
- Cover. We got to find cover. - We can hide in these.
不行
No.
到那里去 快走
There. Come on.
快
Go, go!
- 能不能藏在那边？- 没时间啦
- God, no. Can we hide over there? - No time!
（使用中）
现在
Well.
让我们来估计一下情况
Let's assess the situation.
- 我们完蛋了 - 在厕所里完蛋吗？
- We're screwed. - We're screwed in an outhouse?
- 当初怎么会没拿枪 - 只要一发子弹
- If I had been able to grab just one gun! - Even a single shot.
- 我们要在这里待多久 - 几分钟
- How long are we stuck here? - Minutes.
再过几分钟 我们的体温 会让这里象火炉一样发光
Our combined heat will make this thing glow to them.
那我们就没命的跑
So, we run! We just run like hell!
不行 我们跑不到半英里就会被抓到
No, they fly. We couldn't get haIf a mile.
既不能留又不能走 你说该怎么办
Okay. Can't stay. Can't go. Your turn.
我们和它们决一死战
We've got to fight them.
其实它们并不聪明 而且只能看到热源
They're not that smart. They only see heat.
还有它们的屁会燃烧 可是这有什么帮助？
They light their farts. How does that help?
我想到了
No, wait.
它们等于是易燃性的化学品
They're full of flammable chemicaIs.
若让它们吞下热的东西 就能让它们自动燃烧
Could we ignite them, somehow? Get them to swallow something hot?
- 怎么做呢？- 拿热的东西刺它们
- How? - Stick them with something hot, or a fire.
- 燃烧的矛 - 可是不能太接近它们 否则会被撕成碎片
- A flaming spear. - They'll kill us if we get that close to them!
最好用射的 如果我有…
I'd rather shoot them, somehow. If I just had my…
你没有枪 认了吧
Burt, you don't have a gun. Deal with it.
- 洋芋枪 - 什么？
- A potato gun! - A what?
- 洋芋枪 - 什么枪？
- A potato gun! - What?
小时候你从没做过吗？
Didn't you make one as a kid, Burt?
当时我把我的BB汽枪 改装成全自动的…
I converted my BB gun to full auto…
我们用旧的导管来做
We made them from an old pipe.
先把一边封住 放进几滴点火液
You seal up one end, put in a few drops of lighter fluid…
把洋芋放进去然后点燃 洋芋能飞一百码
stick in the potato, light the touchhole. Potato will go a hundred yards.
只是这次 我们放燃烧箭来代替
Only, instead of a potato, we shoot a flaming arrow.
有何不可
Why not?
好主意
I like it.
那我们得分头去找材料
Yes! Now, of course, we have to do some shopping.
需要导管 任何尺寸都行 做箭的东西 能烧的破布
We need to get some pipe, any size, things for arrows, rags to burn.
还需要汽油…酒精
Then we'll need something for gasoline. Alcohol.
这可不容易 我知道去哪找燃烧液体
This won't be easy.
你们俩去找其他材料
Wait, I got a line on flaming liquid. You two, go for parts.
- 有没有看到屁股开花在附近？- 没有
- You see any of these rocket-butts nearby? - No?
好 那我们出发
No? All right, let's go.
你们要小心
Watch yourselves.
屁股开花 就真让你的屁股开花
Ass-Blaster! Blasted your own damn ass!
怎么回事？
What the hell was that?
- 我杀死一支 我真的杀了一支 - 干得好
- I killed one! I did it! - Way to go, girl
别太高兴 还有三支呢
Don't get cocky! That still leaves three!
反正我杀了一支
I killed one.
你们听着 马上就要天黑了 我们找到多少东西了？
listen up, it'll be dark soon. How are we doing, people?
我找到一些导管 我找到一些破布
I got some pipes. I got some rags.
不错
Good work!
- 还有一些箭 - 我们到黄色卡车那儿集合
- I need some arrows. - Let's meet over at that yellow truck.
先生 我们需要你的帮助
Okay, Nestor, we need your help.
先生 谢谢你
Thanks, Nestor.
伯特 你吓死我了
Burt.
- 杰克怎么还没回来 - 我不知道
- What's taking Jack so long? - I don't know.
- 杰克 你在搞什么？- 够不够？
- Jack! - Is that enough?
足够啦
That will do.
好 现在…
Now, look.
我们到那间活动房屋里
Let's move to that mobile home.
在高地才好发射
It offers high ground for a good line of fire.
快跑
Run!
快 快进来
Come on, Jodi!
锁起来 想吃 门儿都没有
Lock it! Yeah, eat that.
真凶呀
Damn, girl.
我们快开始工作
Come on, let's get to work.
这是属于一个老朋友的 他在第一次突袭蟒攻击中丧生
A friend, Nestor, was killed in the first graboid incursion.
- 活动房屋就搬到这里来 - 他喜欢喝上两杯
- His trailer ended up here. - He loved his shine.
把这些弄断
Here, rip some of these.
再把一端封起来 还要做个点火孔
Now, you have to seal up one end. Also, make a touchhole to light it.
我有概念了
I get the concept.
这些家伙随时会撞破屋顶进来 就象在你家一样
Any minute, this guy will kamikaze through your roof like before.
我需要瞄准器 给我胶布或铁丝都行
All right, I need a gun sight. Anybody grab any tape or wire?
你的耳环 耳环
Your earrings. Your earrings!
把它拿下来 太好了
Take them off. Excellent.
仍旧没有点火孔
Still don't have a touchhole.
这里有个小孔 可以用吗？
This has a little hole. Will this work?
犀利的武器
Armed and dangerous.
- 有打火机吗？- 伯特有
- But do we have a lighter? - Burt does.
伯特有 你怎么知道？
How do you know?
因为你是伯特呀
Well, you're Burt.
说对啦
Damn right I am.
糟糕 神风特攻队来了
Shit! Another kamikaze run!
把威士忌倒到枪管里 这足够发射好几发
Whiskey down the barrel. About a shot's worth.
它就在上空
He knows. He's up!
去开门
Open the door.
门开了
Door open!
它就在那里
There!
- 现在点火吗？- 不 等会儿
- Now? - No, wait for it.
- 现在吗？- 再等一下
- Now? - Wait for it. Wait for it.
点火
Now!
成功了
It worked!
炸它个屁滚尿流 真的把它炸…得屁滚尿流
Blew him away! I mean, blew him…
所以人类才会在 食物链的最上层
That's why we're at the top of the food chain.
死了两个 还剩两个
Two down, and two to go!
重新装箭
Reload.
威士忌
Whiskey.
装箭 装好了
I'll take that arrow. Load it.
会有用的
That will do it.
- 蹲下来 - 我有个主意 把箭点燃
- Get down! Stay down! - No! I got an idea.
- 我们从另一个天窗中射出去 - 伯特 蹲下来
- We'll shoot it through the other skylight. - Stay down, Burt.
- 现在呢？- 把你的腿张开
- Now what? - Spread your legs.
你是什么意思
Excuse me?
好 我懂了
I get it. Okay.
- 没射中可别怪我… - 只要瞄准好就发射
- Don't blame me if I miss because… - Aim and shoot!
好
Okay!
- 你在搞什么鬼 - 我射中它了
- What the hell did you do? - I shot him.
- 伯特 - 伯特
- Burt. - Burt!
哪天我们该一起去打猎
We should go hunting sometime.
把这些拿着
Here you go.
它看起来很生气
I think he looks pissed!
虽然生气但很笨 一定很容易射中
Pissed, but dumb. No sitting duck, Burt?
绝对不要先做假设
Never assume anything.
我一下令就发射 点火
She's ready. Stand by to fire at my command. Light me!
- 不可能 - 正如所料
- No way! - I knew it!
它们永远在学习之中
Sons of bitches are always on a learning curve.
装箭
Load.
它进攻啦
Incoming!
打火机
Lighter.
我需要打火机
I need a lighter.
快闪 它要爆炸了
It's going to blow! Into the back room, now!
快 快走
Get in here.
快走 伯特 到这里来
Go, go! Get in here, Burt!
真恶心
Yuck.
哇 恐怖的经验
Jeez.
现在是二十三点五十九分
Twenty-three hours, 59 minutes.
任务完成了
Mission completed.
是阿白
EI Blanco
为什么它老是知道我在哪里
Damn it! How the hell does he always know where I am?
我的表 它会发出超音波
The watch. The uItrasonic signal.
- 伯特 你没事吧 - 我被卡住了
- Burt! Are you okay? - I'm caught.
它来了 快把表丢掉
Burt, it's coming! Get rid of the watch!
你疯了吗 快离开这里
You're crazy. Get out of here!
阿白 既然你想要就过来拿呀
EI Blanco, you want it? Come get it, dude!
过来拿 来呀
Here you go, buddy!
- 工具在我的口袋里 - 老兄 来拿呀
- My Leatherman tool! In my pocket! - Here you go, little buddy, now!
右边 下排 第三个口袋
Right side, bottom row, third pocket.
- 把卡在我背心上的铁丝切断 - 要怎么打开它
- Cut the springs where my vest is snagged. - How do you open this?
那是什么？
What is that?
快点
Come on.
乔蒂 拜托快点 我正在努力
Jodi, hurry it up! I'm working on it!
一
One.
- 你快走 走呀 - 伯特 你闭嘴
- Get out of here. Go on! - Shut up, Burt!
快点
Come on.
Go on!
全能的神呀
God Almighty!
投得好
Good throw.
在我的旋转肌腱出毛病以前
I used to pitch a little single A ball.
我曾是小联盟的投手
till the old rotator cuff started acting up.
虽然机会不大 但阿白有可能会回来吃第二顿
On the off-chance that EI Blanco's coming back for seconds…
帮我离开这里好吗？
want to get me off this thing?
好
Yes.
请你等一下好吗？
Could you hold on for just a minute?
他们出价跟你一样高
They matched your offer.
抱歉 这可是世界仅有的屁股开花
Well, I'm sorry. This is the world's only living Ass-Blaster.
我还得供女儿上大学
And I have a daughter to put through school.
我要部车
I want a car.
请你等一下
Could you hold a minute?
拉斯维加斯的人出价更高
The Vegas guys went even higher.
要不要接受？
Should we do it?
齐格飞与罗伊 我们决定卖给你们了
Siegfried, Roy, he's all yours.
记住要待在绳子后面
Make sure you stay behind the ropes.
- 沙漠杰克 要走了吗？- 看来恐怕会变成洗车杰克
- Hitting the road, Desert Jack? - Well, more like, Car Wash Jack.
自然界供应一切
The universe provides.
- 恭喜啦 - 谢谢你
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
看来你仍会在这附近 对 我喜欢这里
So, I guess you'll be sticking around.
它提供许多资源
Yeah, I like the area. It has a lot to offer.
我的车加了个新后轴 我带你去
Hey, listen, I'm breaking in my new rear axle. You want to…
- 试车？- 我正忙着装货
- go for a little ride? - I'm restocking.
那边的云很漂亮
Nice clouds out there.
这里就可以看到了
I can see the clouds from here.
可是到那里看更好看
Yeah, but these… See, these are the good ones.
那…
Well…
敏蒂 你帮我看一下店好吗？
Mindy? Can you watch the store?
我就知道
It figures.
成熟女人的魅力
Older women.
阿白先生 下午好
Buenas tardes, Senor Blanco.
乖 跟着车子走就行
That's it, just follow the car.
伯特
Burt!
好车 我一直在等你
Hey, nice wheels. I've been expecting you, Melvin.
你是个顽固的抢钱一族
You are one persistent little money-grubber.
别这样嘛 你看看 这里什么也没有
Come on, Burt. Look around, man. There's nothing here.
我要改变它 好让更多的家庭搬过来住
I'm going to turn this into something. I'll build homes for families.
所以你最好趁机高价卖出
The smart thing for you to do is cash in right now.
- 你最好到我这边来 - 为什么？
- You might want to join me, Melvin. - Why?
这边比较安全
It's safer up here.
天呀 我以为你把它们全杀光了
Jesus Christ, Burt! I thought you killed all those things.
- 我可没这么说 - 快杀它呀 炸死它
- I never said that. - God, man, kill it! Blow it up!
你还在等什么？
What are you waiting for?
问题是只要它存在一天
The thing is, as long as one of these reptilians is still alive…
这整个区域就是被保护区
this whole area is deemed protected.
这是根据濒临绝种动物法中 第1472-B条款
You know, pursuant to section 1472-B of the Endangered Species Act?
换句话说 不准建房子 公寓或是牧场
In other words, no houses, no condos and no ranchettes.
你疯了 这家伙会吃掉你
You're crazy. Okay? These things, man, they're going to…
会把你们全部吃光
They're going to eat you, Burt. They're going to get all of you.
我们有地下监视器 突袭蟒路障和各种保护措施
We got new geophones, graboid barriers, blanket protection.
而且全镇都同意 若在你和阿白中间做选择
The whole town agrees. Between you and EI Blanco,
大家都选择阿白
they'll take him every time.
再见啦 马文
Adi, Melvin!
伯特
Burt! Hey!
Burt!
伯特
你这个混蛋
Burt! You asshole!
你是个笨杂种
You damn son of a bitch!
我恨你 恨你的枪
God! I hate you! I hate your guts!
你是个寒酸 有病
You sorry, sick…
狂妄…右翼 观念狭隘…
paranoid, right-wing…redneck psycho!
神经短路的庄稼汉
Shit-kicker!
该死的伯特
Goddamn you, Burt!
我更恨你那顶帽子
And I hate that hat!